shagcity.co.uk 2018-04-13

# Mature flirting for adults - Find your mature match today at Shagcity.co.uk

### Privacy Policy

Midsummer Online B.V. ("We"), have adopted this Privacy Policy to protect personal information of our users and to let our users know how we might use it. Our Privacy Policy only applies to activities you perform on our Website and not on third parties such as payment providers. This Privacy Policy was implemented on July 1st, 2016 and may change from time to time without notification. Please return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. 

We will continue to have the right to change our privacy policy and practices. 

### IP Address

We may collect and store your IP address during your visit to our Website and its affiliated Services for security and optimization purposes. We reserve the right to, in case of possible fraudulent actions, trace the personal information that belongs to your IP address. 

### Cookies

We use cookies to keep track of all of your activity on our Website, so that we can enhance your experience. We also use cookies to save your password and financial information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you use our Service. Third party advertisers on the Website may also place or read cookies on your browser. Learn more about cookies. 

### Third party links

On the Website, we may place links to other Websites operated by other parties. These third party Websites may contain our brand name and trademarks or other intellectual property that we own; some do not. When you click on these links and are being re-directed to these third party Websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand name, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other Websites or business practices, and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to these third party Websites. These third party Websites may collect different kinds of information about you and may use your information in different ways than we would do, if collected on our Website. We do not accept any responsibility for third party Websites. 

### Personal information

Midsummer Online B.V. is committed to treating your personal information with a high degree of care. Your personal information will never be shared or sold to third parties. 

Your Account is for your individual and personal use only. You may not authorize others to use your Account for any purpose. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of, and restricting access to, your Account and password, and you agree to accept sole responsibility for all activities that occur under your Account or password. 

You confirm that all content and intellectual property rights sent to or trough our Service will be transferred to us. Midsummer Online B.V. thus has the right to use these contributions for commercial purposes. 

### Fraudulent activities

In case of fraudulent activities we have the right to share your information with parties, such as but not limited to: collection agencies, the Police and any relevant authority or enforcement body (including your Internet Service Provider or network administrator). 

If you deny a purchase (illegal activity) that you have made on our Website it may result in legal action towards you, which can lead to prosecution, fines and impairment of your credit rating. You will be added to a card blacklist, which may affect future online card purchases. 

### Payment service providers

To provide you with an excellent service and to operate our Website, including processing transactions and supporting your activities on our Service, we may share your personal information with Payment Service Providers, which provide us with Payment solutions. These entities may not use your personal information for any other purpose than processing your payment. 

### Anonymous message system

We allow our users to exchange anonymous messages through our private messaging system. It is forbidden to post personal contact information such as phone numbers, family names, URL’s or other personal information. We reserve the right to reject, modify, or delete any profile. 

### Photographs

By agreeing to our Privacy Policy, you agree to only upload photographs of adult individuals who are at least 18 years or older. Group photos, photos that feature children and photos that include other recognizable persons may not be used on the Website. We reserve the right to decline and remove any photographs that, in our sole discretion, violate our terms, the law, or do not meet our standards. 

### Marketing

By sharing your personal information with Midsummer Online B.V. you give us the permission to process this data and use it for the following purposes:   
\- Sending newsletters, similar services and moderated e-mails to enhance the adult entertainment experience by our related entities or us.   
\- Transactional e-mails including but limited to messages, likes and sign up confirmation.   
\- Other marketing communications such as related offers, related   
\- Creating user profiles. 

### Public and other demographic information

We may review demographic information. We may use this information to enable other users to find your profile and to determine whether they are a match for you and to communicate with you. We may use demographic information to tailor the Service and communications to your interests. 

### Changing E-mail preferences and personal information

To change your e-mail preferences and personal information you need to log in on our Website. Click on “Settings” to change your e-mail preferences or click on “My Profile” to change your personal information. 

### The Data protection Act 1998

You have the right to access information, which is held about you if exercised in accordance with the Data protection Act 1998. If you want to request access to your personal information, please e-mail support@shagcity.co.uk 

Learn more about the Data protection Act 1998  
https://www.gov.uk/data-protection/the-data-protection-act 

Midsummer Online B.V. has copyright over this Privacy Policy. It is not allowed to use or copy this Privacy Policy. We may take legal action against you if you copy and use our Privacy Policy without our written permission.
